paragraphId	sentenceID	tokenId	beginOffset	endOffset	whitespaceAfter	headTokenId	originalWord	normalizedWord	lemma	pos	ner	deprel	inQuotation	characterId	correctedCharId	ClustersAssignments(,separated)	isRepresentativeOfClusters(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedHeadTokIds(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedDeprels(,separated)	AnimacyAndGender(,separated)
0	0	0	0	1	S	2	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	dep	null
0	0	1	2	8	S	2	Jomari	Jomari	Jomari	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	compound	null
0	0	2	9	15	S	-1	Yllana	Yllana	Yllana	NNP	PERSON	null	false	-1	-1	null	null	-1	root	null
0	0	3	16	18	S	2	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	4	case	null
0	0	4	19	23	S	7	Bert	Bert	Bert	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	nmod:as	null
0	0	5	24	25	S	7	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	7	dep	null
0	0	6	26	33	S	7	Richard	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	7	compound	null
0	0	7	34	43	S	3	Gutierrez	Gutierrez	Gutierrez	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	4	dep	null
0	0	8	44	46	S	3	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	9	case	null
0	0	9	47	53	S	12	Marvin	Marvin	Marvin	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	c1	c1	7	nmod:as	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	10	54	55	S	12	*	*	*	SYM	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	12	dep	null
0	0	11	56	59	S	12	Iza	Iza	Iza	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	12	compound	null
0	0	12	60	67	S	8	Calzado	Calzado	Calzado	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	9	dep	null
0	0	13	68	70	S	8	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	14	case	null
0	0	14	71	75	S	17	Anna	Anna	Anna	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	12	nmod:as	null
0	0	15	76	77	S	17	*	*	*	SYM	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	dep	null
0	0	16	78	83	S	17	Angel	Angel	Angel	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	compound	null
0	0	17	84	90	S	13	Locsin	Locsin	Locsin	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	14	dep	null
0	0	18	91	93	S	13	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	19	case	null
0	0	19	94	99	S	22	Pinky	Pinky	Pinky	NNP	O	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	null	17	nmod:as	(c2;INANIMATE;FEMALE),
0	0	20	100	101	S	22	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	22	dep	null
0	0	21	102	107	S	22	James	James	James	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	22	compound	null
0	0	22	108	114	S	18	Blanco	Blanco	Blanco	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	19	dep	null
0	0	23	115	117	S	18	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	24	case	null
0	0	24	118	122	S	27	Jude	Jude	Jude	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	22	nmod:as	null
0	0	25	123	124	S	27	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	27	dep	null
0	0	26	125	129	S	27	Ella	Ella	Ella	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	27	compound	null
0	0	27	130	137	S	23	Guevara	Guevara	Guevara	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	24	dep	null
0	0	28	138	140	S	23	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	29	case	null
0	0	29	141	145	S	32	Lara	Lara	Lara	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	27	nmod:as	null
0	0	30	146	147	S	32	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	dep	null
0	0	31	148	151	S	32	Lui	Lui	Lui	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	compound	null
0	0	32	152	161	S	28	Manansala	Manansala	Manansala	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	29	dep	null
0	0	33	162	164	S	28	as	as	as	IN	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	36	case	null
0	0	34	165	171		36	Marvin	Marvin	Marvin	NNP	PERSON	poss	false	-1	-1	c1	null	36	nmod:poss	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	35	171	173	S	34	's	's	's	POS	O	possessive	false	-1	-1	c1	null	34	case	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	36	174	180	S	33	Mother	Mother	Mother	NNP	O	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	nmod:as	null
0	0	37	181	182	S	39	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	39	dep	null
0	0	38	183	189	S	39	Tessie	Tessie	Tessie	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	39	compound	null
0	0	39	190	199	S	36	Villarama	Villarama	Villarama	NNP	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	dep	null
0	0	40	200	202	S	39	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	43	case	null
0	0	41	203	208		43	Pinky	Pinky	Pinky	NNP	ORGANIZATION	poss	false	-1	-1	c2	c2	43	nmod:poss	(c2;ANIMATE;FEMALE),
0	0	42	208	210	S	41	's	's	's	POS	O	possessive	false	-1	-1	c2	c2	41	case	(c2;ANIMATE;FEMALE),
0	0	43	211	217	S	40	Mother	Mother	mother	NN	O	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	nmod:as	null
0	0	44	218	219	S	46	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	46	dep	null
0	0	45	220	227	S	46	Pocholo	Pocholo	Pocholo	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	46	compound	null
0	0	46	228	234	S	43	Montes	Montes	Montes	NNP	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	27	dep	null
0	0	47	235	237	S	46	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	50	case	null
0	0	48	238	243		50	Pinky	Pinky	Pinky	NNP	O	poss	false	-1	-1	c2	null	50	nmod:poss	(c2;ANIMATE;FEMALE),
0	0	49	243	245	S	48	's	's	's	POS	O	possessive	false	-1	-1	c2	null	48	case	(c2;ANIMATE;FEMALE),
0	0	50	246	252	N	47	Father	Father	Father	NNP	O	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	27	nmod:as	null
