paragraphId	sentenceID	tokenId	beginOffset	endOffset	whitespaceAfter	headTokenId	originalWord	normalizedWord	lemma	pos	ner	deprel	inQuotation	characterId	correctedCharId	ClustersAssignments(,separated)	isRepresentativeOfClusters(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedHeadTokIds(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedDeprels(,separated)	AnimacyAndGender(,separated)
0	0	0	0	1		2	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	dep	null
0	0	1	1	8	S	2	Richard	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	compound	null
0	0	2	9	13	S	-1	Gere	Gere	Gere	NNP	PERSON	null	false	-1	-1	null	null	-1	root	null
0	0	3	14	16	S	2	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	5	case	null
0	0	4	17	24	S	5	Vincent	Vincent	Vincent	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	5	compound	null
0	0	5	25	32	S	3	Eastman	Eastman	Eastman	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	2	nmod:as	null
0	0	6	33	34		8	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	8	dep	null
0	0	7	34	40	S	8	Sharon	Sharon	Sharon	NNP	ORGANIZATION	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	8	compound	null
0	0	8	41	46	S	5	Stone	Stone	Stone	NNP	ORGANIZATION	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	5	dep	null
0	0	9	47	49	S	8	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	11	case	null
0	0	10	50	55	S	11	Sally	Sally	Sally	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	11	compound	null
0	0	11	56	63	S	9	Eastman	Eastman	Eastman	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	8	nmod:as	null
0	0	12	64	65		14	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	14	dep	null
0	0	13	65	71	S	14	Lolita	Lolita	Lolita	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	14	compound	null
0	0	14	72	82	S	11	Davidovich	Davidovich	Davidovich	NNP	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	11	dep	null
0	0	15	83	85	S	14	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	case	null
0	0	16	86	92	S	17	Olivia	Olivia	Olivia	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	compound	null
0	0	17	93	100	S	15	Marshak	Marshak	Marshak	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	14	nmod:as	null
0	0	18	101	102		20	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	20	dep	null
0	0	19	102	108	S	20	Martin	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	20	compound	null
0	0	20	109	115	S	17	Landau	Landau	Landau	NNP	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	dep	null
0	0	21	116	118	S	20	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	22	case	null
0	0	22	119	123	S	25	Neal	Neal	Neal	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	20	nmod:as	null
0	0	23	124	125		25	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	dep	null
0	0	24	125	130	S	25	David	David	David	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	compound	null
0	0	25	131	136	S	21	Selby	Selby	Selby	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	22	dep	null
0	0	26	137	139	S	31	as	as	as	IN	O	mark	false	-1	-1	null	null	28	case	null
0	0	27	140	147	S	28	Richard	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	28	compound	null
0	0	28	148	154	S	31	Quarry	Quarry	Quarry	NNP	PERSON	nsubj	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	nmod:as	null
0	0	29	155	156		31	*	*	*	SYM	O	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	31	dep	null
0	0	30	156	164	S	31	Jennifer	Jennifer	Jennifer	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	31	compound	null
0	0	31	165	173	S	20	Morrison	Morrison	Morrison	NNP	PERSON	dep	false	-1	-1	null	null	28	dep	null
0	0	32	174	176	S	31	as	as	as	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	34	case	null
0	0	33	177	184	S	34	Meaghan	Meaghan	Meaghan	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	34	compound	null
0	0	34	185	192	N	32	Eastman	Eastman	Eastman	NNP	PERSON	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	31	nmod:as	null
