paragraphId	sentenceID	tokenId	beginOffset	endOffset	whitespaceAfter	headTokenId	originalWord	normalizedWord	lemma	pos	ner	deprel	inQuotation	characterId	correctedCharId	ClustersAssignments(,separated)	isRepresentativeOfClusters(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedHeadTokIds(,separated)	ListOfCollapsedDeprels(,separated)	AnimacyAndGender(,separated)
0	0	0	0	6	S	2	Edward	Edward	Edward	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	c1	c1	2	compound	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	1	7	12	S	2	James	James	James	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	c1	c1	2	compound	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	2	13	18	S	3	Olmos	Olmos	Olmos	NNP	PERSON	nsubj	false	-1	-1	c1	c1	3	nsubj	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	3	19	24	S	-1	plays	plays	play	VBZ	O	null	false	-1	-1	null	null	-1	root	null
0	0	4	25	34	S	6	Detective	Detective	Detective	NNP	O	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	6	compound	null
0	0	5	35	42	S	6	Anthony	Anthony	Anthony	NNP	PERSON	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	c2	6	compound	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	6	43	51		3	Piscotti	Piscotti	Piscotti	NNP	PERSON	dobj	false	-1	-1	c2	c2	3	dobj	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	7	51	52	S	6	,	,	,	,	O	punct	false	-1	-1	null	null	6	punct	null
0	0	8	53	54	S	13	a	a	a	DT	O	det	false	-1	-1	c2	null	13	det	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	9	55	58	S	13	New	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	null	13	compound	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	10	59	63	S	13	York	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	null	13	compound	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	11	64	68	S	13	City	City	City	NNP	LOCATION	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	null	13	compound	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	12	69	75	S	13	police	police	police	NN	O	nn	false	-1	-1	c2	null	13	compound	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	13	76	83		6	officer	officer	officer	NN	O	appos	false	-1	-1	c2	null	6	appos	(c2;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	0	14	83	84	S	3	.	.	.	.	O	punct	false	-1	-1	null	null	3	punct	null
0	1	15	85	87	S	17	He	He	he	PRP	O	nsubj	false	-1	-1	c1	null	17	nsubj	(c1;ANIMATE;MALE),
0	1	16	88	90	S	17	is	is	be	VBZ	O	aux	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	aux	null
0	1	17	91	97	S	-1	trying	trying	try	VBG	O	null	false	-1	-1	null	null	-1	root	null
0	1	18	98	100	S	19	to	to	to	TO	O	aux	false	-1	-1	null	null	19	mark	null
0	1	19	101	106	S	17	crack	crack	crack	VB	O	xcomp	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	xcomp	null
0	1	20	107	110	S	21	the	the	the	DT	O	det	false	-1	-1	null	null	21	det	null
0	1	21	111	117	S	19	taking	taking	taking	NN	O	dobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	19	dobj	null
0	1	22	118	120	S	21	of	of	of	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	case	null
0	1	23	121	122	S	25	a	a	a	DT	O	det	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	det	null
0	1	24	123	129	S	25	subway	subway	subway	NN	O	nn	false	-1	-1	null	null	25	compound	null
0	1	25	130	135	S	22	train	train	train	NN	O	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	21	nmod:of	null
0	1	26	136	141	S	30	where	where	where	WRB	O	advmod	false	-1	-1	null	null	30	advmod	null
0	1	27	142	145	S	28	the	the	the	DT	O	det	false	-1	-1	null	null	28	det	null
0	1	28	146	157	S	30	antagonists	antagonists	antagonist	NNS	O	nsubj	false	-1	-1	null	null	30	nsubj	null
0	1	29	158	161	S	30	are	are	be	VBP	O	aux	false	-1	-1	null	null	30	aux	null
0	1	30	162	169	S	25	holding	holding	hold	VBG	O	rcmod	false	-1	-1	null	null	19	advcl	null
0	1	31	170	173	S	32	the	the	the	DT	O	det	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	det	null
0	1	32	174	184	S	30	passengers	passengers	passenger	NNS	O	dobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	30	dobj	null
0	1	33	185	188	S	32	for	for	for	IN	O	prep	false	-1	-1	null	null	34	case	null
0	1	34	189	195		33	ransom	ransom	ransom	NN	O	pobj	false	-1	-1	null	null	32	nmod:for	null
0	1	35	195	196	N	17	.	.	.	.	O	punct	false	-1	-1	null	null	17	punct	null
